

# Ivan Zabrodin

E-mail: xvanx84@gmail.com Website: <a href="https://ivanzabrodin.com/">https://ivanzabrodin.com/</a>
Phone: +79119423159 Address: Saint-Petersburg, Russia

# Work experience

PayCos 12.05.2020 — Present

Software Engineer

Payment system development, API integration.

Molinos 20.09.2017 — 30.05.2020

Ruby on Rails Developer

Creating web applications on RubyOnRails

Working with API / using and creating / with full documentation

Building a project architecture

Assessing the amount and timing of tasks for the backend

Querying the database (PostgreSQL)

Implementation of VK, Telegram, Facebook Messenger and Viber bots

CashCowPro 25.02.2017 — 31.05.2018

Software Developer

Project: Analytics platform and software tool for online sellers

Responsible for a part of developing highly distributed Ruby on Rails web application for a high performance, high traffic, advanced interactive site that attracts a lot of visitors per day, by providing technical documentation for various products online.

### Brabens Development 04.05.2016 — 15.02.2017

Ruby on Rails Developer

Projects:

Search For Manuals Online

Search For Alternative apps Online

Back-end developing using Ruby on Rails, implementing parsers and crawlers.

# Qualifications

#### Summary:

Software development engineer featuring expertise in Ruby on Rails, web frameworks and other programming languages, a passion for Web 2.0 trends, APIs, mashups and other disruptive technologies.

- Strong knowledge of Web standards and protocols
- Understanding of relation model and its implementations

Ivan Zahrodin

- Knowledges in RESTful API
- Writing technical documentations

Technical skills:

Front-end: HTML5/CSS3, Sass, Haml, JQuery, Twitter Bootstrap

Back-end: Ruby(Ruby on Rails, Sinatra), RDBMS (MySQL, PostgreSQL), RSpec, Nginx, Puma, Redis, Sidekiq, Docker

Cloud infrastructure systems: Heroku, AWS

Tools: Vim, Jira, Trello, Slack

Version control: Git

Automating software building: Bundler, Capistrano, Mina, Rake

#### Core principles:

- Follow CS/software design principles- Design before implementation
- The team is greater than any single person- Testing leads to stable maintainable code

#### Language Skills:

- Russian Native
- English Intermediate

### Education

Ruby on Rails developer Dec 2015 — Mar 2016

GeekBrains

https://geekbrains.ru/

Ruby on Rails developer Apr 2017 — Aug 2017

mkdev

https://mkdev.me/

## **Interests**

- Sport, workouts
- Foreign languages learning

# References

References available upon request.

Ivan Zabrodin